

# **JESSE H. OUDOM**

# JUNIOR WEB DEVELOPER

- in https://www.linkedin.com/in/jesseoudom/
- https://github.com/joudom
- jesse\_oudom@yahoo.com
- +310-465-6420
- Atlanta, GA

#### **Portfolio:**

https://joudom.github.io/JesseOudom/

### **Summary:**

Motivated full-stack developer with project management experience and familiarity with high-paced environments requiring collaboration and communication.

Driven to build applications as part of a team to improve the modern world as well as the future.

#### **Front-End Skills:**

- HTML5
- AJAX
- CSS3
- ReactJS
- Bootstrap 5
- Create React App
- JavaScript
- Redux
- jQuery

## **Back-End Skills:**

- Node.js
- Git
- Express.js
- REST
- PostgreSQL
- Bcrypt
- Sequelize

#### **Education**



### **High School Diploma**

West High School - Torrance, CA Year of Graduation: 2009

#### **Certifications**



## **Certificate of Completion**

DigitalCrafts - Atlanta, GA Year of Graduation: 2022

• 26-wk Full-Stack Web Dev Bootcamp

### **Experience**



### Kuehne + Nagel Inc May 2022 - Present

Customs Entry Writer - East Point, GA

- Process entries for customs release on freight
- Review documentation for US CBP compliance
- Keen attention to details & proactive self-starter



#### **DigitalCrafts**

#### June 2022 - December 2022

Full-Stack Web Developer - Atlanta, GA

# **LocalEyes**

https://github.com/joudom/LocalEyes

- React app allowing users to upload photos & post deals found in their local area
- HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, JavaScript, ReactJS, Git, Node.js, Express.js, Bcrypt, Cors, Google Maps API
- Worked on a team of 3 members with front-end design & back-end queries to a database
- Took lead on developing user authentication
- Took lead on implementing Googles's Map API

#### Drink-182

https://github.com/joudom/Drink-182

- Front-end app allowing users to explore cocktail & meal recipes
- HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, JavaScript, jQuery, Git, Text-to-Speech Reader
- Worked on a team of 3 members with front-end design JavaScript functionality
- Implemented a filter feature that calls an API to display interactive options for users to sort by
- Created a meal feature that displays random images of meals from an API call



# Fluence Energy March 2021 - May 2022

Logistics Specialist - Alpharetta, GA

- Global operations & project management
- Arrange transport of goods to various sites
- Worked on a global team coordinating transportation and insurance on all product
- Developed strong communication & leadership skills in order to meet critical project deadlines
- Collaborated with multiple vendors